{
  "uniqueId": "anagrams8",
  "name": "Anagrams Length 8 Quiz",
  "article": "an",
  "instructions": "Unscramable the below word!",
  "questionCreationStrategy": "IMAGE",
  "dictionaryLinkStrategy": "WEBSTER_ANSWER",
  "answerTimeLimitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "cardPreprocessingStrategy": "RANDOMIZE_QUESTION_CHARACTERS",
  "discordFinalAnswerListElementStrategy": "QUESTION_AND_ANSWER_LINK_ANSWER",
  "scoreAnswerStrategy": "ONE_ANSWER_ONE_POINT",
  "additionalAnswerWaitStrategy": "JAPANESE_SETTINGS",
  "discordIntermediateAnswerListElementStrategy": "CORRECT_ANSWERS",
  "cards": [
    {
      "question": "abdicate",
      "answer": "abdicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "abnormal",
      "answer": "abnormal"
    },
    {
      "question": "abortion",
      "answer": "abortion"
    },
    {
      "question": "abortive",
      "answer": "abortive"
    },
    {
      "question": "abrasive",
      "answer": "abrasive"
    },
    {
      "question": "absolute",
      "answer": "absolute"
    },
    {
      "question": "abstract",
      "answer": "abstract"
    },
    {
      "question": "abundant",
      "answer": "abundant"
    },
    {
      "question": "academic",
      "answer": "academic"
    },
    {
      "question": "accident",
      "answer": "accident"
    },
    {
      "question": "accolade",
      "answer": "accolade"
    },
    {
      "question": "accuracy",
      "answer": "accuracy"
    },
    {
      "question": "accurate",
      "answer": "accurate"
    },
    {
      "question": "accustom",
      "answer": "accustom"
    },
    {
      "question": "acoustic",
      "answer": "acoustic"
    },
    {
      "question": "acquaint",
      "answer": "acquaint"
    },
    {
      "question": "activate",
      "answer": "activate"
    },
    {
      "question": "actively",
      "answer": "actively"
    },
    {
      "question": "activist",
      "answer": "activist"
    },
    {
      "question": "activity",
      "answer": "activity"
    },
    {
      "question": "actually",
      "answer": "actually"
    },
    {
      "question": "addicted",
      "answer": "addicted"
    },
    {
      "question": "addition",
      "answer": "addition"
    },
    {
      "question": "additive",
      "answer": "additive"
    },
    {
      "question": "adequacy",
      "answer": "adequacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "adequate",
      "answer": "adequate"
    },
    {
      "question": "adhesive",
      "answer": "adhesive"
    },
    {
      "question": "adjacent",
      "answer": "adjacent"
    },
    {
      "question": "admonish",
      "answer": "admonish"
    },
    {
      "question": "adoption",
      "answer": "adoption"
    },
    {
      "question": "adorable",
      "answer": "adorable"
    },
    {
      "question": "adultery",
      "answer": "adultery"
    },
    {
      "question": "advanced",
      "answer": "advanced"
    },
    {
      "question": "advisory",
      "answer": "advisory"
    },
    {
      "question": "advocacy",
      "answer": "advocacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "affected",
      "answer": "affected"
    },
    {
      "question": "affinity",
      "answer": "affinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "affluent",
      "answer": "affluent"
    },
    {
      "question": "agrarian",
      "answer": "agrarian"
    },
    {
      "question": "airborne",
      "answer": "airborne"
    },
    {
      "question": "aircraft",
      "answer": "aircraft"
    },
    {
      "question": "airliner",
      "answer": "airliner"
    },
    {
      "question": "airplane",
      "answer": "airplane"
    },
    {
      "question": "airtight",
      "answer": "airtight"
    },
    {
      "question": "alarming",
      "answer": "alarming"
    },
    {
      "question": "alderman",
      "answer": "alderman"
    },
    {
      "question": "alienate",
      "answer": "alienate"
    },
    {
      "question": "allegory",
      "answer": "allegory"
    },
    {
      "question": "allergic",
      "answer": "allergic"
    },
    {
      "question": "alliance",
      "answer": "alliance"
    },
    {
      "question": "alluring",
      "answer": "alluring"
    },
    {
      "question": "allusion",
      "answer": "allusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "almighty",
      "answer": "almighty"
    },
    {
      "question": "alphabet",
      "answer": "alphabet"
    },
    {
      "question": "although",
      "answer": "although"
    },
    {
      "question": "altitude",
      "answer": "altitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "altruism",
      "answer": "altruism"
    },
    {
      "question": "aluminum",
      "answer": "aluminum"
    },
    {
      "question": "ambition",
      "answer": "ambition"
    },
    {
      "question": "amenable",
      "answer": "amenable"
    },
    {
      "question": "analysis",
      "answer": "analysis"
    },
    {
      "question": "ancestor",
      "answer": "ancestor"
    },
    {
      "question": "ancestry",
      "answer": "ancestry"
    },
    {
      "question": "anecdote",
      "answer": "anecdote"
    },
    {
      "question": "animated",
      "answer": "animated"
    },
    {
      "question": "announce",
      "answer": "announce"
    },
    {
      "question": "annoying",
      "answer": "annoying"
    },
    {
      "question": "anorexia",
      "answer": "anorexia"
    },
    {
      "question": "anteroom",
      "answer": "anteroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "antidote",
      "answer": "antidote"
    },
    {
      "question": "anything",
      "answer": "anything"
    },
    {
      "question": "anywhere",
      "answer": "anywhere"
    },
    {
      "question": "aperture",
      "answer": "aperture"
    },
    {
      "question": "apparent",
      "answer": "apparent"
    },
    {
      "question": "appendix",
      "answer": "appendix"
    },
    {
      "question": "appetite",
      "answer": "appetite"
    },
    {
      "question": "applause",
      "answer": "applause"
    },
    {
      "question": "appraise",
      "answer": "appraise"
    },
    {
      "question": "approach",
      "answer": "approach"
    },
    {
      "question": "approval",
      "answer": "approval"
    },
    {
      "question": "aptitude",
      "answer": "aptitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "aquarium",
      "answer": "aquarium"
    },
    {
      "question": "argument",
      "answer": "argument"
    },
    {
      "question": "armament",
      "answer": "armament"
    },
    {
      "question": "armchair",
      "answer": "armchair"
    },
    {
      "question": "arrogant",
      "answer": "arrogant"
    },
    {
      "question": "artifice",
      "answer": "artifice"
    },
    {
      "question": "artistic",
      "answer": "artistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "aspirant",
      "answer": "aspirant"
    },
    {
      "question": "assassin",
      "answer": "assassin"
    },
    {
      "question": "assemble",
      "answer": "assemble"
    },
    {
      "question": "assembly",
      "answer": "assembly"
    },
    {
      "question": "assessor",
      "answer": "assessor"
    },
    {
      "question": "asteroid",
      "answer": "asteroid"
    },
    {
      "question": "astonish",
      "answer": "astonish"
    },
    {
      "question": "athletic",
      "answer": "athletic"
    },
    {
      "question": "atrocity",
      "answer": "atrocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "attitude",
      "answer": "attitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "attorney",
      "answer": "attorney"
    },
    {
      "question": "audacity",
      "answer": "audacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "audience",
      "answer": "audience"
    },
    {
      "question": "audition",
      "answer": "audition"
    },
    {
      "question": "automate",
      "answer": "automate"
    },
    {
      "question": "aversion",
      "answer": "aversion"
    },
    {
      "question": "bachelor",
      "answer": "bachelor"
    },
    {
      "question": "backbone",
      "answer": "backbone"
    },
    {
      "question": "backdrop",
      "answer": "backdrop"
    },
    {
      "question": "backfire",
      "answer": "backfire"
    },
    {
      "question": "backlash",
      "answer": "backlash"
    },
    {
      "question": "backward",
      "answer": "backward"
    },
    {
      "question": "backyard",
      "answer": "backyard"
    },
    {
      "question": "bacteria",
      "answer": "bacteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "bankrupt",
      "answer": "bankrupt"
    },
    {
      "question": "barbecue",
      "answer": "barbecue"
    },
    {
      "question": "barefoot",
      "answer": "barefoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "baseball",
      "answer": "baseball"
    },
    {
      "question": "basement",
      "answer": "basement"
    },
    {
      "question": "bathroom",
      "answer": "bathroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "beginner",
      "answer": "beginner"
    },
    {
      "question": "behavior",
      "answer": "behavior"
    },
    {
      "question": "believer",
      "answer": "believer"
    },
    {
      "question": "bequeath",
      "answer": "bequeath"
    },
    {
      "question": "bereaved",
      "answer": "bereaved"
    },
    {
      "question": "betrayal",
      "answer": "betrayal"
    },
    {
      "question": "beverage",
      "answer": "beverage"
    },
    {
      "question": "birthday",
      "answer": "birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "bitterly",
      "answer": "bitterly"
    },
    {
      "question": "blackout",
      "answer": "blackout"
    },
    {
      "question": "blessing",
      "answer": "blessing"
    },
    {
      "question": "blinding",
      "answer": "blinding"
    },
    {
      "question": "blizzard",
      "answer": "blizzard"
    },
    {
      "question": "blooming",
      "answer": "blooming"
    },
    {
      "question": "boarding",
      "answer": "boarding"
    },
    {
      "question": "boastful",
      "answer": "boastful"
    },
    {
      "question": "boldness",
      "answer": "boldness"
    },
    {
      "question": "bookcase",
      "answer": "bookcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "bookshop",
      "answer": "bookshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "borrower",
      "answer": "borrower"
    },
    {
      "question": "botanist",
      "answer": "botanist"
    },
    {
      "question": "boundary",
      "answer": "boundary"
    },
    {
      "question": "boutique",
      "answer": "boutique"
    },
    {
      "question": "bracelet",
      "answer": "bracelet"
    },
    {
      "question": "brandish",
      "answer": "brandish"
    },
    {
      "question": "breaking",
      "answer": "breaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "breakout",
      "answer": "breakout"
    },
    {
      "question": "breeding",
      "answer": "breeding"
    },
    {
      "question": "brethren",
      "answer": "brethren"
    },
    {
      "question": "briefing",
      "answer": "briefing"
    },
    {
      "question": "brighten",
      "answer": "brighten"
    },
    {
      "question": "brightly",
      "answer": "brightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "broccoli",
      "answer": "broccoli"
    },
    {
      "question": "brochure",
      "answer": "brochure"
    },
    {
      "question": "buddhism",
      "answer": "buddhism"
    },
    {
      "question": "buddhist",
      "answer": "buddhist"
    },
    {
      "question": "building",
      "answer": "building"
    },
    {
      "question": "bulletin",
      "answer": "bulletin"
    },
    {
      "question": "business",
      "answer": "business"
    },
    {
      "question": "buttress",
      "answer": "buttress"
    },
    {
      "question": "calamity",
      "answer": "calamity"
    },
    {
      "question": "calculus",
      "answer": "calculus"
    },
    {
      "question": "calendar",
      "answer": "calendar"
    },
    {
      "question": "calmness",
      "answer": "calmness"
    },
    {
      "question": "campaign",
      "answer": "campaign"
    },
    {
      "question": "canaille",
      "answer": "canaille"
    },
    {
      "question": "capacity",
      "answer": "capacity"
    },
    {
      "question": "cardigan",
      "answer": "cardigan"
    },
    {
      "question": "cardinal",
      "answer": "cardinal"
    },
    {
      "question": "carefree",
      "answer": "carefree"
    },
    {
      "question": "careless",
      "answer": "careless"
    },
    {
      "question": "carousel",
      "answer": "carousel"
    },
    {
      "question": "carriage",
      "answer": "carriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "cassette",
      "answer": "cassette"
    },
    {
      "question": "casually",
      "answer": "casually"
    },
    {
      "question": "catalyst",
      "answer": "catalyst"
    },
    {
      "question": "catapult",
      "answer": "catapult"
    },
    {
      "question": "cataract",
      "answer": "cataract"
    },
    {
      "question": "category",
      "answer": "category"
    },
    {
      "question": "catholic",
      "answer": "catholic"
    },
    {
      "question": "cautious",
      "answer": "cautious"
    },
    {
      "question": "cavalier",
      "answer": "cavalier"
    },
    {
      "question": "cellular",
      "answer": "cellular"
    },
    {
      "question": "cemetery",
      "answer": "cemetery"
    },
    {
      "question": "centered",
      "answer": "centered"
    },
    {
      "question": "cerebral",
      "answer": "cerebral"
    },
    {
      "question": "ceremony",
      "answer": "ceremony"
    },
    {
      "question": "chairman",
      "answer": "chairman"
    },
    {
      "question": "champion",
      "answer": "champion"
    },
    {
      "question": "chaplain",
      "answer": "chaplain"
    },
    {
      "question": "charming",
      "answer": "charming"
    },
    {
      "question": "chastise",
      "answer": "chastise"
    },
    {
      "question": "cheerful",
      "answer": "cheerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "chemical",
      "answer": "chemical"
    },
    {
      "question": "chestnut",
      "answer": "chestnut"
    },
    {
      "question": "childish",
      "answer": "childish"
    },
    {
      "question": "children",
      "answer": "children"
    },
    {
      "question": "chivalry",
      "answer": "chivalry"
    },
    {
      "question": "chlorine",
      "answer": "chlorine"
    },
    {
      "question": "christen",
      "answer": "christen"
    },
    {
      "question": "circular",
      "answer": "circular"
    },
    {
      "question": "citation",
      "answer": "citation"
    },
    {
      "question": "civilian",
      "answer": "civilian"
    },
    {
      "question": "civility",
      "answer": "civility"
    },
    {
      "question": "civilize",
      "answer": "civilize"
    },
    {
      "question": "claimant",
      "answer": "claimant"
    },
    {
      "question": "clarinet",
      "answer": "clarinet"
    },
    {
      "question": "classify",
      "answer": "classify"
    },
    {
      "question": "cleaning",
      "answer": "cleaning"
    },
    {
      "question": "clearing",
      "answer": "clearing"
    },
    {
      "question": "cleavage",
      "answer": "cleavage"
    },
    {
      "question": "climatic",
      "answer": "climatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "climbing",
      "answer": "climbing"
    },
    {
      "question": "clinical",
      "answer": "clinical"
    },
    {
      "question": "clothing",
      "answer": "clothing"
    },
    {
      "question": "coalesce",
      "answer": "coalesce"
    },
    {
      "question": "cocktail",
      "answer": "cocktail"
    },
    {
      "question": "coercion",
      "answer": "coercion"
    },
    {
      "question": "cohesion",
      "answer": "cohesion"
    },
    {
      "question": "coincide",
      "answer": "coincide"
    },
    {
      "question": "collapse",
      "answer": "collapse"
    },
    {
      "question": "colonial",
      "answer": "colonial"
    },
    {
      "question": "colonist",
      "answer": "colonist"
    },
    {
      "question": "colorful",
      "answer": "colorful"
    },
    {
      "question": "coloring",
      "answer": "coloring"
    },
    {
      "question": "colossal",
      "answer": "colossal"
    },
    {
      "question": "comatose",
      "answer": "comatose"
    },
    {
      "question": "combined",
      "answer": "combined"
    },
    {
      "question": "comeback",
      "answer": "comeback"
    },
    {
      "question": "comedian",
      "answer": "comedian"
    },
    {
      "question": "commando",
      "answer": "commando"
    },
    {
      "question": "commence",
      "answer": "commence"
    },
    {
      "question": "commerce",
      "answer": "commerce"
    },
    {
      "question": "commoner",
      "answer": "commoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "commonly",
      "answer": "commonly"
    },
    {
      "question": "communal",
      "answer": "communal"
    },
    {
      "question": "commuter",
      "answer": "commuter"
    },
    {
      "question": "complain",
      "answer": "complain"
    },
    {
      "question": "complete",
      "answer": "complete"
    },
    {
      "question": "composed",
      "answer": "composed"
    },
    {
      "question": "composer",
      "answer": "composer"
    },
    {
      "question": "compound",
      "answer": "compound"
    },
    {
      "question": "comprise",
      "answer": "comprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "computer",
      "answer": "computer"
    },
    {
      "question": "conceive",
      "answer": "conceive"
    },
    {
      "question": "concerto",
      "answer": "concerto"
    },
    {
      "question": "conclude",
      "answer": "conclude"
    },
    {
      "question": "concrete",
      "answer": "concrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "condense",
      "answer": "condense"
    },
    {
      "question": "confetti",
      "answer": "confetti"
    },
    {
      "question": "conflict",
      "answer": "conflict"
    },
    {
      "question": "confound",
      "answer": "confound"
    },
    {
      "question": "confront",
      "answer": "confront"
    },
    {
      "question": "confused",
      "answer": "confused"
    },
    {
      "question": "congress",
      "answer": "congress"
    },
    {
      "question": "conquest",
      "answer": "conquest"
    },
    {
      "question": "conserve",
      "answer": "conserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "consider",
      "answer": "consider"
    },
    {
      "question": "constant",
      "answer": "constant"
    },
    {
      "question": "construe",
      "answer": "construe"
    },
    {
      "question": "consumer",
      "answer": "consumer"
    },
    {
      "question": "contempt",
      "answer": "contempt"
    },
    {
      "question": "continue",
      "answer": "continue"
    },
    {
      "question": "contract",
      "answer": "contract"
    },
    {
      "question": "contrary",
      "answer": "contrary"
    },
    {
      "question": "contrast",
      "answer": "contrast"
    },
    {
      "question": "contrive",
      "answer": "contrive"
    },
    {
      "question": "converge",
      "answer": "converge"
    },
    {
      "question": "converse",
      "answer": "converse"
    },
    {
      "question": "convince",
      "answer": "convince"
    },
    {
      "question": "coolness",
      "answer": "coolness"
    },
    {
      "question": "coronary",
      "answer": "coronary"
    },
    {
      "question": "corporal",
      "answer": "corporal"
    },
    {
      "question": "corridor",
      "answer": "corridor"
    },
    {
      "question": "cosmetic",
      "answer": "cosmetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "courtesy",
      "answer": "courtesy"
    },
    {
      "question": "covenant",
      "answer": "covenant"
    },
    {
      "question": "coverage",
      "answer": "coverage"
    },
    {
      "question": "covering",
      "answer": "covering"
    },
    {
      "question": "cowardly",
      "answer": "cowardly"
    },
    {
      "question": "creation",
      "answer": "creation"
    },
    {
      "question": "creature",
      "answer": "creature"
    },
    {
      "question": "creditor",
      "answer": "creditor"
    },
    {
      "question": "crescent",
      "answer": "crescent"
    },
    {
      "question": "criminal",
      "answer": "criminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "critical",
      "answer": "critical"
    },
    {
      "question": "crossing",
      "answer": "crossing"
    },
    {
      "question": "cucumber",
      "answer": "cucumber"
    },
    {
      "question": "culinary",
      "answer": "culinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "cultural",
      "answer": "cultural"
    },
    {
      "question": "cupboard",
      "answer": "cupboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "currency",
      "answer": "currency"
    },
    {
      "question": "customer",
      "answer": "customer"
    },
    {
      "question": "cylinder",
      "answer": "cylinder"
    },
    {
      "question": "cynicism",
      "answer": "cynicism"
    },
    {
      "question": "daffodil",
      "answer": "daffodil"
    },
    {
      "question": "darkness",
      "answer": "darkness"
    },
    {
      "question": "database",
      "answer": "database"
    },
    {
      "question": "daughter",
      "answer": "daughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "daunting",
      "answer": "daunting"
    },
    {
      "question": "daybreak",
      "answer": "daybreak"
    },
    {
      "question": "daylight",
      "answer": "daylight"
    },
    {
      "question": "deadline",
      "answer": "deadline"
    },
    {
      "question": "deceased",
      "answer": "deceased"
    },
    {
      "question": "december",
      "answer": "december"
    },
    {
      "question": "decimate",
      "answer": "decimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "decipher",
      "answer": "decipher"
    },
    {
      "question": "decision",
      "answer": "decision"
    },
    {
      "question": "decisive",
      "answer": "decisive"
    },
    {
      "question": "decorate",
      "answer": "decorate"
    },
    {
      "question": "decrease",
      "answer": "decrease"
    },
    {
      "question": "decrepit",
      "answer": "decrepit"
    },
    {
      "question": "dedicate",
      "answer": "dedicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "defender",
      "answer": "defender"
    },
    {
      "question": "defiance",
      "answer": "defiance"
    },
    {
      "question": "definite",
      "answer": "definite"
    },
    {
      "question": "dejected",
      "answer": "dejected"
    },
    {
      "question": "delegate",
      "answer": "delegate"
    },
    {
      "question": "delicate",
      "answer": "delicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "delirium",
      "answer": "delirium"
    },
    {
      "question": "delivery",
      "answer": "delivery"
    },
    {
      "question": "demeanor",
      "answer": "demeanor"
    },
    {
      "question": "dementia",
      "answer": "dementia"
    },
    {
      "question": "democrat",
      "answer": "democrat"
    },
    {
      "question": "demolish",
      "answer": "demolish"
    },
    {
      "question": "demoniac",
      "answer": "demoniac"
    },
    {
      "question": "demurrer",
      "answer": "demurrer"
    },
    {
      "question": "denounce",
      "answer": "denounce"
    },
    {
      "question": "depraved",
      "answer": "depraved"
    },
    {
      "question": "derelict",
      "answer": "derelict"
    },
    {
      "question": "derision",
      "answer": "derision"
    },
    {
      "question": "derisive",
      "answer": "derisive"
    },
    {
      "question": "describe",
      "answer": "describe"
    },
    {
      "question": "deserted",
      "answer": "deserted"
    },
    {
      "question": "desirous",
      "answer": "desirous"
    },
    {
      "question": "desolate",
      "answer": "desolate"
    },
    {
      "question": "despotic",
      "answer": "despotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "destined",
      "answer": "destined"
    },
    {
      "question": "detailed",
      "answer": "detailed"
    },
    {
      "question": "detector",
      "answer": "detector"
    },
    {
      "question": "devotion",
      "answer": "devotion"
    },
    {
      "question": "diabetes",
      "answer": "diabetes"
    },
    {
      "question": "diabetic",
      "answer": "diabetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "diabolic",
      "answer": "diabolic"
    },
    {
      "question": "diagnose",
      "answer": "diagnose"
    },
    {
      "question": "diagonal",
      "answer": "diagonal"
    },
    {
      "question": "dialogue",
      "answer": "dialogue"
    },
    {
      "question": "diameter",
      "answer": "diameter"
    },
    {
      "question": "diarrhea",
      "answer": "diarrhea"
    },
    {
      "question": "diastole",
      "answer": "diastole"
    },
    {
      "question": "diligent",
      "answer": "diligent"
    },
    {
      "question": "diminish",
      "answer": "diminish"
    },
    {
      "question": "dinosaur",
      "answer": "dinosaur"
    },
    {
      "question": "diplomat",
      "answer": "diplomat"
    },
    {
      "question": "directly",
      "answer": "directly"
    },
    {
      "question": "director",
      "answer": "director"
    },
    {
      "question": "disagree",
      "answer": "disagree"
    },
    {
      "question": "disaster",
      "answer": "disaster"
    },
    {
      "question": "disciple",
      "answer": "disciple"
    },
    {
      "question": "disclose",
      "answer": "disclose"
    },
    {
      "question": "discount",
      "answer": "discount"
    },
    {
      "question": "discover",
      "answer": "discover"
    },
    {
      "question": "discreet",
      "answer": "discreet"
    },
    {
      "question": "discrete",
      "answer": "discrete"
    },
    {
      "question": "disgrace",
      "answer": "disgrace"
    },
    {
      "question": "disguise",
      "answer": "disguise"
    },
    {
      "question": "dishonor",
      "answer": "dishonor"
    },
    {
      "question": "dislodge",
      "answer": "dislodge"
    },
    {
      "question": "disorder",
      "answer": "disorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "dispatch",
      "answer": "dispatch"
    },
    {
      "question": "disperse",
      "answer": "disperse"
    },
    {
      "question": "displace",
      "answer": "displace"
    },
    {
      "question": "disposal",
      "answer": "disposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "disquiet",
      "answer": "disquiet"
    },
    {
      "question": "dissolve",
      "answer": "dissolve"
    },
    {
      "question": "distance",
      "answer": "distance"
    },
    {
      "question": "distaste",
      "answer": "distaste"
    },
    {
      "question": "distinct",
      "answer": "distinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "distract",
      "answer": "distract"
    },
    {
      "question": "distress",
      "answer": "distress"
    },
    {
      "question": "district",
      "answer": "district"
    },
    {
      "question": "distrust",
      "answer": "distrust"
    },
    {
      "question": "dividend",
      "answer": "dividend"
    },
    {
      "question": "division",
      "answer": "division"
    },
    {
      "question": "doctrine",
      "answer": "doctrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "document",
      "answer": "document"
    },
    {
      "question": "dogmatic",
      "answer": "dogmatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "doldrums",
      "answer": "doldrums"
    },
    {
      "question": "domestic",
      "answer": "domestic"
    },
    {
      "question": "domicile",
      "answer": "domicile"
    },
    {
      "question": "dominant",
      "answer": "dominant"
    },
    {
      "question": "dominate",
      "answer": "dominate"
    },
    {
      "question": "dominion",
      "answer": "dominion"
    },
    {
      "question": "donation",
      "answer": "donation"
    },
    {
      "question": "doorbell",
      "answer": "doorbell"
    },
    {
      "question": "doorstep",
      "answer": "doorstep"
    },
    {
      "question": "doubtful",
      "answer": "doubtful"
    },
    {
      "question": "downcast",
      "answer": "downcast"
    },
    {
      "question": "downfall",
      "answer": "downfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "downplay",
      "answer": "downplay"
    },
    {
      "question": "downtown",
      "answer": "downtown"
    },
    {
      "question": "downward",
      "answer": "downward"
    },
    {
      "question": "dramatic",
      "answer": "dramatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "drawback",
      "answer": "drawback"
    },
    {
      "question": "dreadful",
      "answer": "dreadful"
    },
    {
      "question": "dressing",
      "answer": "dressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "drinking",
      "answer": "drinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "dripping",
      "answer": "dripping"
    },
    {
      "question": "driveway",
      "answer": "driveway"
    },
    {
      "question": "dropping",
      "answer": "dropping"
    },
    {
      "question": "drudgery",
      "answer": "drudgery"
    },
    {
      "question": "duckling",
      "answer": "duckling"
    },
    {
      "question": "dullness",
      "answer": "dullness"
    },
    {
      "question": "duration",
      "answer": "duration"
    },
    {
      "question": "dwelling",
      "answer": "dwelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "eastward",
      "answer": "eastward"
    },
    {
      "question": "eclectic",
      "answer": "eclectic"
    },
    {
      "question": "economic",
      "answer": "economic"
    },
    {
      "question": "ecstatic",
      "answer": "ecstatic"
    },
    {
      "question": "educated",
      "answer": "educated"
    },
    {
      "question": "educator",
      "answer": "educator"
    },
    {
      "question": "efficacy",
      "answer": "efficacy"
    },
    {
      "question": "eggplant",
      "answer": "eggplant"
    },
    {
      "question": "egoistic",
      "answer": "egoistic"
    },
    {
      "question": "eighteen",
      "answer": "eighteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "election",
      "answer": "election"
    },
    {
      "question": "elective",
      "answer": "elective"
    },
    {
      "question": "electric",
      "answer": "electric"
    },
    {
      "question": "electron",
      "answer": "electron"
    },
    {
      "question": "elephant",
      "answer": "elephant"
    },
    {
      "question": "elevated",
      "answer": "elevated"
    },
    {
      "question": "elevator",
      "answer": "elevator"
    },
    {
      "question": "eleventh",
      "answer": "eleventh"
    },
    {
      "question": "eligible",
      "answer": "eligible"
    },
    {
      "question": "eloquent",
      "answer": "eloquent"
    },
    {
      "question": "embezzle",
      "answer": "embezzle"
    },
    {
      "question": "emigrant",
      "answer": "emigrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "eminence",
      "answer": "eminence"
    },
    {
      "question": "emissary",
      "answer": "emissary"
    },
    {
      "question": "emission",
      "answer": "emission"
    },
    {
      "question": "emphasis",
      "answer": "emphasis"
    },
    {
      "question": "employee",
      "answer": "employee"
    },
    {
      "question": "employer",
      "answer": "employer"
    },
    {
      "question": "encircle",
      "answer": "encircle"
    },
    {
      "question": "encroach",
      "answer": "encroach"
    },
    {
      "question": "endeavor",
      "answer": "endeavor"
    },
    {
      "question": "engaging",
      "answer": "engaging"
    },
    {
      "question": "engender",
      "answer": "engender"
    },
    {
      "question": "engineer",
      "answer": "engineer"
    },
    {
      "question": "enormous",
      "answer": "enormous"
    },
    {
      "question": "ensemble",
      "answer": "ensemble"
    },
    {
      "question": "enshrine",
      "answer": "enshrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "entirely",
      "answer": "entirely"
    },
    {
      "question": "entrance",
      "answer": "entrance"
    },
    {
      "question": "entrench",
      "answer": "entrench"
    },
    {
      "question": "envelope",
      "answer": "envelope"
    },
    {
      "question": "environs",
      "answer": "environs"
    },
    {
      "question": "envisage",
      "answer": "envisage"
    },
    {
      "question": "envision",
      "answer": "envision"
    },
    {
      "question": "epilepsy",
      "answer": "epilepsy"
    },
    {
      "question": "equality",
      "answer": "equality"
    },
    {
      "question": "equalize",
      "answer": "equalize"
    },
    {
      "question": "equation",
      "answer": "equation"
    },
    {
      "question": "erection",
      "answer": "erection"
    },
    {
      "question": "escallop",
      "answer": "escallop"
    },
    {
      "question": "escapade",
      "answer": "escapade"
    },
    {
      "question": "esoteric",
      "answer": "esoteric"
    },
    {
      "question": "estimate",
      "answer": "estimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "estrange",
      "answer": "estrange"
    },
    {
      "question": "ethereal",
      "answer": "ethereal"
    },
    {
      "question": "euphoria",
      "answer": "euphoria"
    },
    {
      "question": "evacuate",
      "answer": "evacuate"
    },
    {
      "question": "evaluate",
      "answer": "evaluate"
    },
    {
      "question": "eventful",
      "answer": "eventful"
    },
    {
      "question": "eventual",
      "answer": "eventual"
    },
    {
      "question": "everyday",
      "answer": "everyday"
    },
    {
      "question": "everyone",
      "answer": "everyone"
    },
    {
      "question": "eviction",
      "answer": "eviction"
    },
    {
      "question": "evidence",
      "answer": "evidence"
    },
    {
      "question": "exacting",
      "answer": "exacting"
    },
    {
      "question": "examiner",
      "answer": "examiner"
    },
    {
      "question": "excavate",
      "answer": "excavate"
    },
    {
      "question": "exchange",
      "answer": "exchange"
    },
    {
      "question": "exciting",
      "answer": "exciting"
    },
    {
      "question": "exemplar",
      "answer": "exemplar"
    },
    {
      "question": "exercise",
      "answer": "exercise"
    },
    {
      "question": "exertion",
      "answer": "exertion"
    },
    {
      "question": "existent",
      "answer": "existent"
    },
    {
      "question": "existing",
      "answer": "existing"
    },
    {
      "question": "exorcise",
      "answer": "exorcise"
    },
    {
      "question": "expedite",
      "answer": "expedite"
    },
    {
      "question": "explorer",
      "answer": "explorer"
    },
    {
      "question": "exponent",
      "answer": "exponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "exporter",
      "answer": "exporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "exposure",
      "answer": "exposure"
    },
    {
      "question": "extended",
      "answer": "extended"
    },
    {
      "question": "exterior",
      "answer": "exterior"
    },
    {
      "question": "external",
      "answer": "external"
    },
    {
      "question": "eyesight",
      "answer": "eyesight"
    },
    {
      "question": "fabulous",
      "answer": "fabulous"
    },
    {
      "question": "facility",
      "answer": "facility"
    },
    {
      "question": "fairness",
      "answer": "fairness"
    },
    {
      "question": "faithful",
      "answer": "faithful"
    },
    {
      "question": "familiar",
      "answer": "familiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "farewell",
      "answer": "farewell"
    },
    {
      "question": "farmland",
      "answer": "farmland"
    },
    {
      "question": "farthest",
      "answer": "farthest"
    },
    {
      "question": "fastener",
      "answer": "fastener"
    },
    {
      "question": "favorite",
      "answer": "favorite"
    },
    {
      "question": "fearless",
      "answer": "fearless"
    },
    {
      "question": "feasible",
      "answer": "feasible"
    },
    {
      "question": "february",
      "answer": "february"
    },
    {
      "question": "feedback",
      "answer": "feedback"
    },
    {
      "question": "feminine",
      "answer": "feminine"
    },
    {
      "question": "feminist",
      "answer": "feminist"
    },
    {
      "question": "ferocity",
      "answer": "ferocity"
    },
    {
      "question": "festival",
      "answer": "festival"
    },
    {
      "question": "feverish",
      "answer": "feverish"
    },
    {
      "question": "fidelity",
      "answer": "fidelity"
    },
    {
      "question": "fiftieth",
      "answer": "fiftieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "fineness",
      "answer": "fineness"
    },
    {
      "question": "firework",
      "answer": "firework"
    },
    {
      "question": "flagrant",
      "answer": "flagrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "flagship",
      "answer": "flagship"
    },
    {
      "question": "flashing",
      "answer": "flashing"
    },
    {
      "question": "flattery",
      "answer": "flattery"
    },
    {
      "question": "flawless",
      "answer": "flawless"
    },
    {
      "question": "fleeting",
      "answer": "fleeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "flexible",
      "answer": "flexible"
    },
    {
      "question": "flippant",
      "answer": "flippant"
    },
    {
      "question": "floating",
      "answer": "floating"
    },
    {
      "question": "flooring",
      "answer": "flooring"
    },
    {
      "question": "flounder",
      "answer": "flounder"
    },
    {
      "question": "flourish",
      "answer": "flourish"
    },
    {
      "question": "fluoride",
      "answer": "fluoride"
    },
    {
      "question": "folklore",
      "answer": "folklore"
    },
    {
      "question": "follower",
      "answer": "follower"
    },
    {
      "question": "football",
      "answer": "football"
    },
    {
      "question": "foothold",
      "answer": "foothold"
    },
    {
      "question": "footnote",
      "answer": "footnote"
    },
    {
      "question": "footpath",
      "answer": "footpath"
    },
    {
      "question": "footstep",
      "answer": "footstep"
    },
    {
      "question": "forceful",
      "answer": "forceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "forcible",
      "answer": "forcible"
    },
    {
      "question": "forecast",
      "answer": "forecast"
    },
    {
      "question": "forehead",
      "answer": "forehead"
    },
    {
      "question": "foremost",
      "answer": "foremost"
    },
    {
      "question": "forensic",
      "answer": "forensic"
    },
    {
      "question": "foretell",
      "answer": "foretell"
    },
    {
      "question": "formerly",
      "answer": "formerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "fortieth",
      "answer": "fortieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "fortress",
      "answer": "fortress"
    },
    {
      "question": "fountain",
      "answer": "fountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "fourteen",
      "answer": "fourteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "fraction",
      "answer": "fraction"
    },
    {
      "question": "fracture",
      "answer": "fracture"
    },
    {
      "question": "fragment",
      "answer": "fragment"
    },
    {
      "question": "fragrant",
      "answer": "fragrant"
    },
    {
      "question": "freezing",
      "answer": "freezing"
    },
    {
      "question": "frequent",
      "answer": "frequent"
    },
    {
      "question": "freshman",
      "answer": "freshman"
    },
    {
      "question": "friction",
      "answer": "friction"
    },
    {
      "question": "friendly",
      "answer": "friendly"
    },
    {
      "question": "frighten",
      "answer": "frighten"
    },
    {
      "question": "frontier",
      "answer": "frontier"
    },
    {
      "question": "fruitful",
      "answer": "fruitful"
    },
    {
      "question": "fugitive",
      "answer": "fugitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "function",
      "answer": "function"
    },
    {
      "question": "furlough",
      "answer": "furlough"
    },
    {
      "question": "fuselage",
      "answer": "fuselage"
    },
    {
      "question": "futility",
      "answer": "futility"
    },
    {
      "question": "gangster",
      "answer": "gangster"
    },
    {
      "question": "gardener",
      "answer": "gardener"
    },
    {
      "question": "garrison",
      "answer": "garrison"
    },
    {
      "question": "gasoline",
      "answer": "gasoline"
    },
    {
      "question": "gauntlet",
      "answer": "gauntlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "generate",
      "answer": "generate"
    },
    {
      "question": "generous",
      "answer": "generous"
    },
    {
      "question": "genetics",
      "answer": "genetics"
    },
    {
      "question": "geometry",
      "answer": "geometry"
    },
    {
      "question": "gigantic",
      "answer": "gigantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "gingerly",
      "answer": "gingerly"
    },
    {
      "question": "glorious",
      "answer": "glorious"
    },
    {
      "question": "glossary",
      "answer": "glossary"
    },
    {
      "question": "goldfish",
      "answer": "goldfish"
    },
    {
      "question": "goodness",
      "answer": "goodness"
    },
    {
      "question": "gorgeous",
      "answer": "gorgeous"
    },
    {
      "question": "governor",
      "answer": "governor"
    },
    {
      "question": "graceful",
      "answer": "graceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "gracious",
      "answer": "gracious"
    },
    {
      "question": "gradient",
      "answer": "gradient"
    },
    {
      "question": "graduate",
      "answer": "graduate"
    },
    {
      "question": "graffiti",
      "answer": "graffiti"
    },
    {
      "question": "granddad",
      "answer": "granddad"
    },
    {
      "question": "grandeur",
      "answer": "grandeur"
    },
    {
      "question": "grandson",
      "answer": "grandson"
    },
    {
      "question": "graphite",
      "answer": "graphite"
    },
    {
      "question": "grateful",
      "answer": "grateful"
    },
    {
      "question": "gratuity",
      "answer": "gratuity"
    },
    {
      "question": "greeting",
      "answer": "greeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "grouping",
      "answer": "grouping"
    },
    {
      "question": "grudging",
      "answer": "grudging"
    },
    {
      "question": "grueling",
      "answer": "grueling"
    },
    {
      "question": "gruesome",
      "answer": "gruesome"
    },
    {
      "question": "guardian",
      "answer": "guardian"
    },
    {
      "question": "guidance",
      "answer": "guidance"
    },
    {
      "question": "gullible",
      "answer": "gullible"
    },
    {
      "question": "habitual",
      "answer": "habitual"
    },
    {
      "question": "hallmark",
      "answer": "hallmark"
    },
    {
      "question": "handbook",
      "answer": "handbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "handcuff",
      "answer": "handcuff"
    },
    {
      "question": "handicap",
      "answer": "handicap"
    },
    {
      "question": "handling",
      "answer": "handling"
    },
    {
      "question": "handmade",
      "answer": "handmade"
    },
    {
      "question": "handsome",
      "answer": "handsome"
    },
    {
      "question": "hardness",
      "answer": "hardness"
    },
    {
      "question": "hardship",
      "answer": "hardship"
    },
    {
      "question": "hardware",
      "answer": "hardware"
    },
    {
      "question": "harmless",
      "answer": "harmless"
    },
    {
      "question": "headache",
      "answer": "headache"
    },
    {
      "question": "headline",
      "answer": "headline"
    },
    {
      "question": "headlong",
      "answer": "headlong"
    },
    {
      "question": "heartily",
      "answer": "heartily"
    },
    {
      "question": "heavenly",
      "answer": "heavenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "hedgehog",
      "answer": "hedgehog"
    },
    {
      "question": "hedonism",
      "answer": "hedonism"
    },
    {
      "question": "hegemony",
      "answer": "hegemony"
    },
    {
      "question": "heighten",
      "answer": "heighten"
    },
    {
      "question": "helpless",
      "answer": "helpless"
    },
    {
      "question": "heredity",
      "answer": "heredity"
    },
    {
      "question": "heritage",
      "answer": "heritage"
    },
    {
      "question": "hesitate",
      "answer": "hesitate"
    },
    {
      "question": "highland",
      "answer": "highland"
    },
    {
      "question": "highness",
      "answer": "highness"
    },
    {
      "question": "hillside",
      "answer": "hillside"
    },
    {
      "question": "historic",
      "answer": "historic"
    },
    {
      "question": "holiness",
      "answer": "holiness"
    },
    {
      "question": "homeless",
      "answer": "homeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "homemade",
      "answer": "homemade"
    },
    {
      "question": "homeroom",
      "answer": "homeroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "homesick",
      "answer": "homesick"
    },
    {
      "question": "hometown",
      "answer": "hometown"
    },
    {
      "question": "homework",
      "answer": "homework"
    },
    {
      "question": "homicide",
      "answer": "homicide"
    },
    {
      "question": "honestly",
      "answer": "honestly"
    },
    {
      "question": "hopeless",
      "answer": "hopeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "horrible",
      "answer": "horrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "horseman",
      "answer": "horseman"
    },
    {
      "question": "hospital",
      "answer": "hospital"
    },
    {
      "question": "humanist",
      "answer": "humanist"
    },
    {
      "question": "humanity",
      "answer": "humanity"
    },
    {
      "question": "humility",
      "answer": "humility"
    },
    {
      "question": "humorous",
      "answer": "humorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "hydrogen",
      "answer": "hydrogen"
    },
    {
      "question": "hypnosis",
      "answer": "hypnosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "hysteria",
      "answer": "hysteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "idealist",
      "answer": "idealist"
    },
    {
      "question": "idealize",
      "answer": "idealize"
    },
    {
      "question": "identify",
      "answer": "identify"
    },
    {
      "question": "identity",
      "answer": "identity"
    },
    {
      "question": "ideology",
      "answer": "ideology"
    },
    {
      "question": "idleness",
      "answer": "idleness"
    },
    {
      "question": "ignorant",
      "answer": "ignorant"
    },
    {
      "question": "illusion",
      "answer": "illusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "immature",
      "answer": "immature"
    },
    {
      "question": "imminent",
      "answer": "imminent"
    },
    {
      "question": "immortal",
      "answer": "immortal"
    },
    {
      "question": "immunity",
      "answer": "immunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "immunize",
      "answer": "immunize"
    },
    {
      "question": "imperial",
      "answer": "imperial"
    },
    {
      "question": "impolite",
      "answer": "impolite"
    },
    {
      "question": "imposing",
      "answer": "imposing"
    },
    {
      "question": "impotent",
      "answer": "impotent"
    },
    {
      "question": "imprison",
      "answer": "imprison"
    },
    {
      "question": "improper",
      "answer": "improper"
    },
    {
      "question": "impudent",
      "answer": "impudent"
    },
    {
      "question": "impunity",
      "answer": "impunity"
    },
    {
      "question": "inactive",
      "answer": "inactive"
    },
    {
      "question": "incident",
      "answer": "incident"
    },
    {
      "question": "inclined",
      "answer": "inclined"
    },
    {
      "question": "increase",
      "answer": "increase"
    },
    {
      "question": "indecent",
      "answer": "indecent"
    },
    {
      "question": "indicate",
      "answer": "indicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "indirect",
      "answer": "indirect"
    },
    {
      "question": "indolent",
      "answer": "indolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "industry",
      "answer": "industry"
    },
    {
      "question": "infamous",
      "answer": "infamous"
    },
    {
      "question": "infantry",
      "answer": "infantry"
    },
    {
      "question": "inferior",
      "answer": "inferior"
    },
    {
      "question": "infinite",
      "answer": "infinite"
    },
    {
      "question": "infinity",
      "answer": "infinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "informal",
      "answer": "informal"
    },
    {
      "question": "informed",
      "answer": "informed"
    },
    {
      "question": "infrared",
      "answer": "infrared"
    },
    {
      "question": "infringe",
      "answer": "infringe"
    },
    {
      "question": "infusion",
      "answer": "infusion"
    },
    {
      "question": "inherent",
      "answer": "inherent"
    },
    {
      "question": "iniquity",
      "answer": "iniquity"
    },
    {
      "question": "initiate",
      "answer": "initiate"
    },
    {
      "question": "innocent",
      "answer": "innocent"
    },
    {
      "question": "innuendo",
      "answer": "innuendo"
    },
    {
      "question": "inscribe",
      "answer": "inscribe"
    },
    {
      "question": "insecure",
      "answer": "insecure"
    },
    {
      "question": "insolent",
      "answer": "insolent"
    },
    {
      "question": "insomnia",
      "answer": "insomnia"
    },
    {
      "question": "instance",
      "answer": "instance"
    },
    {
      "question": "instinct",
      "answer": "instinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "instruct",
      "answer": "instruct"
    },
    {
      "question": "insulate",
      "answer": "insulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "integral",
      "answer": "integral"
    },
    {
      "question": "intended",
      "answer": "intended"
    },
    {
      "question": "interest",
      "answer": "interest"
    },
    {
      "question": "interior",
      "answer": "interior"
    },
    {
      "question": "internal",
      "answer": "internal"
    },
    {
      "question": "interval",
      "answer": "interval"
    },
    {
      "question": "intimate",
      "answer": "intimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "intrepid",
      "answer": "intrepid"
    },
    {
      "question": "intrigue",
      "answer": "intrigue"
    },
    {
      "question": "inundate",
      "answer": "inundate"
    },
    {
      "question": "invasion",
      "answer": "invasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "inventor",
      "answer": "inventor"
    },
    {
      "question": "investor",
      "answer": "investor"
    },
    {
      "question": "involved",
      "answer": "involved"
    },
    {
      "question": "ironical",
      "answer": "ironical"
    },
    {
      "question": "irrigate",
      "answer": "irrigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "irritate",
      "answer": "irritate"
    },
    {
      "question": "jealousy",
      "answer": "jealousy"
    },
    {
      "question": "jeopardy",
      "answer": "jeopardy"
    },
    {
      "question": "jettison",
      "answer": "jettison"
    },
    {
      "question": "jubilant",
      "answer": "jubilant"
    },
    {
      "question": "judgment",
      "answer": "judgment"
    },
    {
      "question": "junction",
      "answer": "junction"
    },
    {
      "question": "kangaroo",
      "answer": "kangaroo"
    },
    {
      "question": "kerosene",
      "answer": "kerosene"
    },
    {
      "question": "keyboard",
      "answer": "keyboard"
    },
    {
      "question": "kickback",
      "answer": "kickback"
    },
    {
      "question": "kilogram",
      "answer": "kilogram"
    },
    {
      "question": "kindness",
      "answer": "kindness"
    },
    {
      "question": "knitting",
      "answer": "knitting"
    },
    {
      "question": "knockout",
      "answer": "knockout"
    },
    {
      "question": "lamppost",
      "answer": "lamppost"
    },
    {
      "question": "landlord",
      "answer": "landlord"
    },
    {
      "question": "language",
      "answer": "language"
    },
    {
      "question": "languish",
      "answer": "languish"
    },
    {
      "question": "latitude",
      "answer": "latitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "laudable",
      "answer": "laudable"
    },
    {
      "question": "laughter",
      "answer": "laughter"
    },
    {
      "question": "laureate",
      "answer": "laureate"
    },
    {
      "question": "lavatory",
      "answer": "lavatory"
    },
    {
      "question": "learning",
      "answer": "learning"
    },
    {
      "question": "lecturer",
      "answer": "lecturer"
    },
    {
      "question": "leftover",
      "answer": "leftover"
    },
    {
      "question": "legality",
      "answer": "legality"
    },
    {
      "question": "lemonade",
      "answer": "lemonade"
    },
    {
      "question": "lengthen",
      "answer": "lengthen"
    },
    {
      "question": "leukemia",
      "answer": "leukemia"
    },
    {
      "question": "leverage",
      "answer": "leverage"
    },
    {
      "question": "lifeboat",
      "answer": "lifeboat"
    },
    {
      "question": "lifeless",
      "answer": "lifeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "lifelike",
      "answer": "lifelike"
    },
    {
      "question": "lifelong",
      "answer": "lifelong"
    },
    {
      "question": "lifetime",
      "answer": "lifetime"
    },
    {
      "question": "ligament",
      "answer": "ligament"
    },
    {
      "question": "lighting",
      "answer": "lighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "likewise",
      "answer": "likewise"
    },
    {
      "question": "lingerie",
      "answer": "lingerie"
    },
    {
      "question": "linguist",
      "answer": "linguist"
    },
    {
      "question": "lipstick",
      "answer": "lipstick"
    },
    {
      "question": "listener",
      "answer": "listener"
    },
    {
      "question": "listless",
      "answer": "listless"
    },
    {
      "question": "literary",
      "answer": "literary"
    },
    {
      "question": "litigant",
      "answer": "litigant"
    },
    {
      "question": "localize",
      "answer": "localize"
    },
    {
      "question": "location",
      "answer": "location"
    },
    {
      "question": "lonesome",
      "answer": "lonesome"
    },
    {
      "question": "longtime",
      "answer": "longtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "loophole",
      "answer": "loophole"
    },
    {
      "question": "lordship",
      "answer": "lordship"
    },
    {
      "question": "loyalist",
      "answer": "loyalist"
    },
    {
      "question": "lukewarm",
      "answer": "lukewarm"
    },
    {
      "question": "luncheon",
      "answer": "luncheon"
    },
    {
      "question": "mackerel",
      "answer": "mackerel"
    },
    {
      "question": "magazine",
      "answer": "magazine"
    },
    {
      "question": "magician",
      "answer": "magician"
    },
    {
      "question": "magnetic",
      "answer": "magnetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "magnolia",
      "answer": "magnolia"
    },
    {
      "question": "mainland",
      "answer": "mainland"
    },
    {
      "question": "maintain",
      "answer": "maintain"
    },
    {
      "question": "majority",
      "answer": "majority"
    },
    {
      "question": "maneuver",
      "answer": "maneuver"
    },
    {
      "question": "manifest",
      "answer": "manifest"
    },
    {
      "question": "marathon",
      "answer": "marathon"
    },
    {
      "question": "maritime",
      "answer": "maritime"
    },
    {
      "question": "marriage",
      "answer": "marriage"
    },
    {
      "question": "massacre",
      "answer": "massacre"
    },
    {
      "question": "masterly",
      "answer": "masterly"
    },
    {
      "question": "matching",
      "answer": "matching"
    },
    {
      "question": "material",
      "answer": "material"
    },
    {
      "question": "maternal",
      "answer": "maternal"
    },
    {
      "question": "mattress",
      "answer": "mattress"
    },
    {
      "question": "maturity",
      "answer": "maturity"
    },
    {
      "question": "maverick",
      "answer": "maverick"
    },
    {
      "question": "maximize",
      "answer": "maximize"
    },
    {
      "question": "meantime",
      "answer": "meantime"
    },
    {
      "question": "mechanic",
      "answer": "mechanic"
    },
    {
      "question": "mediator",
      "answer": "mediator"
    },
    {
      "question": "medicate",
      "answer": "medicate"
    },
    {
      "question": "medicine",
      "answer": "medicine"
    },
    {
      "question": "medieval",
      "answer": "medieval"
    },
    {
      "question": "mediocre",
      "answer": "mediocre"
    },
    {
      "question": "meditate",
      "answer": "meditate"
    },
    {
      "question": "meltdown",
      "answer": "meltdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "membrane",
      "answer": "membrane"
    },
    {
      "question": "memorial",
      "answer": "memorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "memorize",
      "answer": "memorize"
    },
    {
      "question": "mentally",
      "answer": "mentally"
    },
    {
      "question": "merchant",
      "answer": "merchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "merciful",
      "answer": "merciful"
    },
    {
      "question": "metallic",
      "answer": "metallic"
    },
    {
      "question": "metaphor",
      "answer": "metaphor"
    },
    {
      "question": "midnight",
      "answer": "midnight"
    },
    {
      "question": "militant",
      "answer": "militant"
    },
    {
      "question": "military",
      "answer": "military"
    },
    {
      "question": "mindless",
      "answer": "mindless"
    },
    {
      "question": "minister",
      "answer": "minister"
    },
    {
      "question": "ministry",
      "answer": "ministry"
    },
    {
      "question": "minority",
      "answer": "minority"
    },
    {
      "question": "mischief",
      "answer": "mischief"
    },
    {
      "question": "misplace",
      "answer": "misplace"
    },
    {
      "question": "misshape",
      "answer": "misshape"
    },
    {
      "question": "mistaken",
      "answer": "mistaken"
    },
    {
      "question": "mistress",
      "answer": "mistress"
    },
    {
      "question": "mistrust",
      "answer": "mistrust"
    },
    {
      "question": "mitigate",
      "answer": "mitigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "mobilize",
      "answer": "mobilize"
    },
    {
      "question": "moderate",
      "answer": "moderate"
    },
    {
      "question": "modestly",
      "answer": "modestly"
    },
    {
      "question": "modulate",
      "answer": "modulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "moisture",
      "answer": "moisture"
    },
    {
      "question": "molecule",
      "answer": "molecule"
    },
    {
      "question": "momentum",
      "answer": "momentum"
    },
    {
      "question": "monarchy",
      "answer": "monarchy"
    },
    {
      "question": "monastic",
      "answer": "monastic"
    },
    {
      "question": "monetary",
      "answer": "monetary"
    },
    {
      "question": "monopoly",
      "answer": "monopoly"
    },
    {
      "question": "monotone",
      "answer": "monotone"
    },
    {
      "question": "monotony",
      "answer": "monotony"
    },
    {
      "question": "monument",
      "answer": "monument"
    },
    {
      "question": "morality",
      "answer": "morality"
    },
    {
      "question": "moreover",
      "answer": "moreover"
    },
    {
      "question": "moribund",
      "answer": "moribund"
    },
    {
      "question": "mortgage",
      "answer": "mortgage"
    },
    {
      "question": "mortuary",
      "answer": "mortuary"
    },
    {
      "question": "mosquito",
      "answer": "mosquito"
    },
    {
      "question": "motherly",
      "answer": "motherly"
    },
    {
      "question": "motivate",
      "answer": "motivate"
    },
    {
      "question": "motorcar",
      "answer": "motorcar"
    },
    {
      "question": "motorist",
      "answer": "motorist"
    },
    {
      "question": "motorway",
      "answer": "motorway"
    },
    {
      "question": "mountain",
      "answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "question": "mounting",
      "answer": "mounting"
    },
    {
      "question": "mournful",
      "answer": "mournful"
    },
    {
      "question": "mouthful",
      "answer": "mouthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "movement",
      "answer": "movement"
    },
    {
      "question": "multiple",
      "answer": "multiple"
    },
    {
      "question": "multiply",
      "answer": "multiply"
    },
    {
      "question": "muscular",
      "answer": "muscular"
    },
    {
      "question": "mushroom",
      "answer": "mushroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "musician",
      "answer": "musician"
    },
    {
      "question": "mustache",
      "answer": "mustache"
    },
    {
      "question": "mutation",
      "answer": "mutation"
    },
    {
      "question": "mutilate",
      "answer": "mutilate"
    },
    {
      "question": "mythical",
      "answer": "mythical"
    },
    {
      "question": "narcotic",
      "answer": "narcotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "national",
      "answer": "national"
    },
    {
      "question": "navigate",
      "answer": "navigate"
    },
    {
      "question": "neatherd",
      "answer": "neatherd"
    },
    {
      "question": "necklace",
      "answer": "necklace"
    },
    {
      "question": "needless",
      "answer": "needless"
    },
    {
      "question": "negative",
      "answer": "negative"
    },
    {
      "question": "neighbor",
      "answer": "neighbor"
    },
    {
      "question": "neurosis",
      "answer": "neurosis"
    },
    {
      "question": "neurotic",
      "answer": "neurotic"
    },
    {
      "question": "newcomer",
      "answer": "newcomer"
    },
    {
      "question": "nickname",
      "answer": "nickname"
    },
    {
      "question": "nineteen",
      "answer": "nineteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "nitrogen",
      "answer": "nitrogen"
    },
    {
      "question": "nobility",
      "answer": "nobility"
    },
    {
      "question": "nobleman",
      "answer": "nobleman"
    },
    {
      "question": "nominate",
      "answer": "nominate"
    },
    {
      "question": "nonsense",
      "answer": "nonsense"
    },
    {
      "question": "normally",
      "answer": "normally"
    },
    {
      "question": "northern",
      "answer": "northern"
    },
    {
      "question": "notarial",
      "answer": "notarial"
    },
    {
      "question": "notebook",
      "answer": "notebook"
    },
    {
      "question": "notional",
      "answer": "notional"
    },
    {
      "question": "novelist",
      "answer": "novelist"
    },
    {
      "question": "november",
      "answer": "november"
    },
    {
      "question": "nowadays",
      "answer": "nowadays"
    },
    {
      "question": "nuisance",
      "answer": "nuisance"
    },
    {
      "question": "numerous",
      "answer": "numerous"
    },
    {
      "question": "nutrient",
      "answer": "nutrient"
    },
    {
      "question": "obedient",
      "answer": "obedient"
    },
    {
      "question": "obituary",
      "answer": "obituary"
    },
    {
      "question": "oblivion",
      "answer": "oblivion"
    },
    {
      "question": "observer",
      "answer": "observer"
    },
    {
      "question": "obsolete",
      "answer": "obsolete"
    },
    {
      "question": "obstacle",
      "answer": "obstacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "obstruct",
      "answer": "obstruct"
    },
    {
      "question": "occasion",
      "answer": "occasion"
    },
    {
      "question": "occupant",
      "answer": "occupant"
    },
    {
      "question": "offender",
      "answer": "offender"
    },
    {
      "question": "offering",
      "answer": "offering"
    },
    {
      "question": "official",
      "answer": "official"
    },
    {
      "question": "offshoot",
      "answer": "offshoot"
    },
    {
      "question": "offshore",
      "answer": "offshore"
    },
    {
      "question": "ointment",
      "answer": "ointment"
    },
    {
      "question": "omelette",
      "answer": "omelette"
    },
    {
      "question": "omission",
      "answer": "omission"
    },
    {
      "question": "onlooker",
      "answer": "onlooker"
    },
    {
      "question": "operator",
      "answer": "operator"
    },
    {
      "question": "opponent",
      "answer": "opponent"
    },
    {
      "question": "opposite",
      "answer": "opposite"
    },
    {
      "question": "optimism",
      "answer": "optimism"
    },
    {
      "question": "optimist",
      "answer": "optimist"
    },
    {
      "question": "optional",
      "answer": "optional"
    },
    {
      "question": "ordinary",
      "answer": "ordinary"
    },
    {
      "question": "organism",
      "answer": "organism"
    },
    {
      "question": "organist",
      "answer": "organist"
    },
    {
      "question": "organize",
      "answer": "organize"
    },
    {
      "question": "oriental",
      "answer": "oriental"
    },
    {
      "question": "original",
      "answer": "original"
    },
    {
      "question": "ornament",
      "answer": "ornament"
    },
    {
      "question": "orthodox",
      "answer": "orthodox"
    },
    {
      "question": "outbreak",
      "answer": "outbreak"
    },
    {
      "question": "outburst",
      "answer": "outburst"
    },
    {
      "question": "outdoors",
      "answer": "outdoors"
    },
    {
      "question": "outgoing",
      "answer": "outgoing"
    },
    {
      "question": "outright",
      "answer": "outright"
    },
    {
      "question": "outsider",
      "answer": "outsider"
    },
    {
      "question": "outskirt",
      "answer": "outskirt"
    },
    {
      "question": "outstrip",
      "answer": "outstrip"
    },
    {
      "question": "outweigh",
      "answer": "outweigh"
    },
    {
      "question": "overcoat",
      "answer": "overcoat"
    },
    {
      "question": "overcome",
      "answer": "overcome"
    },
    {
      "question": "overdose",
      "answer": "overdose"
    },
    {
      "question": "overflow",
      "answer": "overflow"
    },
    {
      "question": "overhaul",
      "answer": "overhaul"
    },
    {
      "question": "overhead",
      "answer": "overhead"
    },
    {
      "question": "overhear",
      "answer": "overhear"
    },
    {
      "question": "overload",
      "answer": "overload"
    },
    {
      "question": "overlook",
      "answer": "overlook"
    },
    {
      "question": "overrate",
      "answer": "overrate"
    },
    {
      "question": "override",
      "answer": "override"
    },
    {
      "question": "overseas",
      "answer": "overseas"
    },
    {
      "question": "overtake",
      "answer": "overtake"
    },
    {
      "question": "overtime",
      "answer": "overtime"
    },
    {
      "question": "overtone",
      "answer": "overtone"
    },
    {
      "question": "overture",
      "answer": "overture"
    },
    {
      "question": "overturn",
      "answer": "overturn"
    },
    {
      "question": "overview",
      "answer": "overview"
    },
    {
      "question": "overwork",
      "answer": "overwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "pacifist",
      "answer": "pacifist"
    },
    {
      "question": "painting",
      "answer": "painting"
    },
    {
      "question": "palpable",
      "answer": "palpable"
    },
    {
      "question": "pamphlet",
      "answer": "pamphlet"
    },
    {
      "question": "panorama",
      "answer": "panorama"
    },
    {
      "question": "paradigm",
      "answer": "paradigm"
    },
    {
      "question": "paradise",
      "answer": "paradise"
    },
    {
      "question": "parallel",
      "answer": "parallel"
    },
    {
      "question": "paralyze",
      "answer": "paralyze"
    },
    {
      "question": "paranoia",
      "answer": "paranoia"
    },
    {
      "question": "parasite",
      "answer": "parasite"
    },
    {
      "question": "particle",
      "answer": "particle"
    },
    {
      "question": "partisan",
      "answer": "partisan"
    },
    {
      "question": "passable",
      "answer": "passable"
    },
    {
      "question": "passbook",
      "answer": "passbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "passport",
      "answer": "passport"
    },
    {
      "question": "password",
      "answer": "password"
    },
    {
      "question": "paternal",
      "answer": "paternal"
    },
    {
      "question": "pathetic",
      "answer": "pathetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "patience",
      "answer": "patience"
    },
    {
      "question": "pavement",
      "answer": "pavement"
    },
    {
      "question": "peaceful",
      "answer": "peaceful"
    },
    {
      "question": "peculiar",
      "answer": "peculiar"
    },
    {
      "question": "pedagogy",
      "answer": "pedagogy"
    },
    {
      "question": "pedantic",
      "answer": "pedantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "pedestal",
      "answer": "pedestal"
    },
    {
      "question": "pedigree",
      "answer": "pedigree"
    },
    {
      "question": "penchant",
      "answer": "penchant"
    },
    {
      "question": "pendulum",
      "answer": "pendulum"
    },
    {
      "question": "perceive",
      "answer": "perceive"
    },
    {
      "question": "periodic",
      "answer": "periodic"
    },
    {
      "question": "permeate",
      "answer": "permeate"
    },
    {
      "question": "personal",
      "answer": "personal"
    },
    {
      "question": "persuade",
      "answer": "persuade"
    },
    {
      "question": "perverse",
      "answer": "perverse"
    },
    {
      "question": "petition",
      "answer": "petition"
    },
    {
      "question": "petulant",
      "answer": "petulant"
    },
    {
      "question": "pheasant",
      "answer": "pheasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "phonetic",
      "answer": "phonetic"
    },
    {
      "question": "physical",
      "answer": "physical"
    },
    {
      "question": "piercing",
      "answer": "piercing"
    },
    {
      "question": "pinnacle",
      "answer": "pinnacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "pinpoint",
      "answer": "pinpoint"
    },
    {
      "question": "pipeline",
      "answer": "pipeline"
    },
    {
      "question": "pitiless",
      "answer": "pitiless"
    },
    {
      "question": "planning",
      "answer": "planning"
    },
    {
      "question": "platform",
      "answer": "platform"
    },
    {
      "question": "platonic",
      "answer": "platonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "playmate",
      "answer": "playmate"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleading",
      "answer": "pleading"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasant",
      "answer": "pleasant"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasing",
      "answer": "pleasing"
    },
    {
      "question": "pleasure",
      "answer": "pleasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "plethora",
      "answer": "plethora"
    },
    {
      "question": "poignant",
      "answer": "poignant"
    },
    {
      "question": "polarize",
      "answer": "polarize"
    },
    {
      "question": "polished",
      "answer": "polished"
    },
    {
      "question": "politics",
      "answer": "politics"
    },
    {
      "question": "polyglot",
      "answer": "polyglot"
    },
    {
      "question": "populous",
      "answer": "populous"
    },
    {
      "question": "porridge",
      "answer": "porridge"
    },
    {
      "question": "portable",
      "answer": "portable"
    },
    {
      "question": "portrait",
      "answer": "portrait"
    },
    {
      "question": "position",
      "answer": "position"
    },
    {
      "question": "positive",
      "answer": "positive"
    },
    {
      "question": "possible",
      "answer": "possible"
    },
    {
      "question": "possibly",
      "answer": "possibly"
    },
    {
      "question": "postcard",
      "answer": "postcard"
    },
    {
      "question": "postpone",
      "answer": "postpone"
    },
    {
      "question": "powerful",
      "answer": "powerful"
    },
    {
      "question": "practice",
      "answer": "practice"
    },
    {
      "question": "precinct",
      "answer": "precinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "precious",
      "answer": "precious"
    },
    {
      "question": "preclude",
      "answer": "preclude"
    },
    {
      "question": "predator",
      "answer": "predator"
    },
    {
      "question": "pregnant",
      "answer": "pregnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "premiere",
      "answer": "premiere"
    },
    {
      "question": "prenatal",
      "answer": "prenatal"
    },
    {
      "question": "presence",
      "answer": "presence"
    },
    {
      "question": "preserve",
      "answer": "preserve"
    },
    {
      "question": "pressing",
      "answer": "pressing"
    },
    {
      "question": "pressure",
      "answer": "pressure"
    },
    {
      "question": "prestige",
      "answer": "prestige"
    },
    {
      "question": "pretense",
      "answer": "pretense"
    },
    {
      "question": "previous",
      "answer": "previous"
    },
    {
      "question": "princess",
      "answer": "princess"
    },
    {
      "question": "printing",
      "answer": "printing"
    },
    {
      "question": "priority",
      "answer": "priority"
    },
    {
      "question": "prisoner",
      "answer": "prisoner"
    },
    {
      "question": "pristine",
      "answer": "pristine"
    },
    {
      "question": "probable",
      "answer": "probable"
    },
    {
      "question": "probably",
      "answer": "probably"
    },
    {
      "question": "proclaim",
      "answer": "proclaim"
    },
    {
      "question": "prodigal",
      "answer": "prodigal"
    },
    {
      "question": "producer",
      "answer": "producer"
    },
    {
      "question": "profound",
      "answer": "profound"
    },
    {
      "question": "progress",
      "answer": "progress"
    },
    {
      "question": "prohibit",
      "answer": "prohibit"
    },
    {
      "question": "prolific",
      "answer": "prolific"
    },
    {
      "question": "promoter",
      "answer": "promoter"
    },
    {
      "question": "promptly",
      "answer": "promptly"
    },
    {
      "question": "properly",
      "answer": "properly"
    },
    {
      "question": "property",
      "answer": "property"
    },
    {
      "question": "proposal",
      "answer": "proposal"
    },
    {
      "question": "prospect",
      "answer": "prospect"
    },
    {
      "question": "protocol",
      "answer": "protocol"
    },
    {
      "question": "protrude",
      "answer": "protrude"
    },
    {
      "question": "provided",
      "answer": "provided"
    },
    {
      "question": "provider",
      "answer": "provider"
    },
    {
      "question": "province",
      "answer": "province"
    },
    {
      "question": "publicly",
      "answer": "publicly"
    },
    {
      "question": "pullover",
      "answer": "pullover"
    },
    {
      "question": "punctual",
      "answer": "punctual"
    },
    {
      "question": "puncture",
      "answer": "puncture"
    },
    {
      "question": "punitive",
      "answer": "punitive"
    },
    {
      "question": "purchase",
      "answer": "purchase"
    },
    {
      "question": "putative",
      "answer": "putative"
    },
    {
      "question": "puzzling",
      "answer": "puzzling"
    },
    {
      "question": "quagmire",
      "answer": "quagmire"
    },
    {
      "question": "quantity",
      "answer": "quantity"
    },
    {
      "question": "question",
      "answer": "question"
    },
    {
      "question": "railroad",
      "answer": "railroad"
    },
    {
      "question": "raincoat",
      "answer": "raincoat"
    },
    {
      "question": "raindrop",
      "answer": "raindrop"
    },
    {
      "question": "rainfall",
      "answer": "rainfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "rational",
      "answer": "rational"
    },
    {
      "question": "reaction",
      "answer": "reaction"
    },
    {
      "question": "reactive",
      "answer": "reactive"
    },
    {
      "question": "readable",
      "answer": "readable"
    },
    {
      "question": "reappear",
      "answer": "reappear"
    },
    {
      "question": "reassure",
      "answer": "reassure"
    },
    {
      "question": "rebuttal",
      "answer": "rebuttal"
    },
    {
      "question": "receiver",
      "answer": "receiver"
    },
    {
      "question": "recently",
      "answer": "recently"
    },
    {
      "question": "receptor",
      "answer": "receptor"
    },
    {
      "question": "recharge",
      "answer": "recharge"
    },
    {
      "question": "reckless",
      "answer": "reckless"
    },
    {
      "question": "recorder",
      "answer": "recorder"
    },
    {
      "question": "recourse",
      "answer": "recourse"
    },
    {
      "question": "recovery",
      "answer": "recovery"
    },
    {
      "question": "regiment",
      "answer": "regiment"
    },
    {
      "question": "regional",
      "answer": "regional"
    },
    {
      "question": "register",
      "answer": "register"
    },
    {
      "question": "registry",
      "answer": "registry"
    },
    {
      "question": "regulate",
      "answer": "regulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "rehearse",
      "answer": "rehearse"
    },
    {
      "question": "reindeer",
      "answer": "reindeer"
    },
    {
      "question": "relation",
      "answer": "relation"
    },
    {
      "question": "relative",
      "answer": "relative"
    },
    {
      "question": "relaxing",
      "answer": "relaxing"
    },
    {
      "question": "relegate",
      "answer": "relegate"
    },
    {
      "question": "relevant",
      "answer": "relevant"
    },
    {
      "question": "reliable",
      "answer": "reliable"
    },
    {
      "question": "relieved",
      "answer": "relieved"
    },
    {
      "question": "religion",
      "answer": "religion"
    },
    {
      "question": "remember",
      "answer": "remember"
    },
    {
      "question": "reminder",
      "answer": "reminder"
    },
    {
      "question": "renegade",
      "answer": "renegade"
    },
    {
      "question": "renounce",
      "answer": "renounce"
    },
    {
      "question": "renovate",
      "answer": "renovate"
    },
    {
      "question": "renowned",
      "answer": "renowned"
    },
    {
      "question": "repeated",
      "answer": "repeated"
    },
    {
      "question": "reporter",
      "answer": "reporter"
    },
    {
      "question": "reprieve",
      "answer": "reprieve"
    },
    {
      "question": "reproach",
      "answer": "reproach"
    },
    {
      "question": "republic",
      "answer": "republic"
    },
    {
      "question": "research",
      "answer": "research"
    },
    {
      "question": "resemble",
      "answer": "resemble"
    },
    {
      "question": "reserved",
      "answer": "reserved"
    },
    {
      "question": "resident",
      "answer": "resident"
    },
    {
      "question": "residual",
      "answer": "residual"
    },
    {
      "question": "resigned",
      "answer": "resigned"
    },
    {
      "question": "resonant",
      "answer": "resonant"
    },
    {
      "question": "resource",
      "answer": "resource"
    },
    {
      "question": "response",
      "answer": "response"
    },
    {
      "question": "restless",
      "answer": "restless"
    },
    {
      "question": "restrain",
      "answer": "restrain"
    },
    {
      "question": "restrict",
      "answer": "restrict"
    },
    {
      "question": "retarded",
      "answer": "retarded"
    },
    {
      "question": "retiring",
      "answer": "retiring"
    },
    {
      "question": "retrieve",
      "answer": "retrieve"
    },
    {
      "question": "reversal",
      "answer": "reversal"
    },
    {
      "question": "reviewer",
      "answer": "reviewer"
    },
    {
      "question": "revolver",
      "answer": "revolver"
    },
    {
      "question": "rhetoric",
      "answer": "rhetoric"
    },
    {
      "question": "rhythmic",
      "answer": "rhythmic"
    },
    {
      "question": "ridicule",
      "answer": "ridicule"
    },
    {
      "question": "rigorous",
      "answer": "rigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "roadside",
      "answer": "roadside"
    },
    {
      "question": "romantic",
      "answer": "romantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "rotation",
      "answer": "rotation"
    },
    {
      "question": "royalist",
      "answer": "royalist"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruminate",
      "answer": "ruminate"
    },
    {
      "question": "ruthless",
      "answer": "ruthless"
    },
    {
      "question": "sabotage",
      "answer": "sabotage"
    },
    {
      "question": "salaried",
      "answer": "salaried"
    },
    {
      "question": "salesman",
      "answer": "salesman"
    },
    {
      "question": "salutary",
      "answer": "salutary"
    },
    {
      "question": "sampling",
      "answer": "sampling"
    },
    {
      "question": "sanction",
      "answer": "sanction"
    },
    {
      "question": "sanctity",
      "answer": "sanctity"
    },
    {
      "question": "sandwich",
      "answer": "sandwich"
    },
    {
      "question": "sanguine",
      "answer": "sanguine"
    },
    {
      "question": "sanitary",
      "answer": "sanitary"
    },
    {
      "question": "sardonic",
      "answer": "sardonic"
    },
    {
      "question": "saturate",
      "answer": "saturate"
    },
    {
      "question": "saturday",
      "answer": "saturday"
    },
    {
      "question": "scarcely",
      "answer": "scarcely"
    },
    {
      "question": "scathing",
      "answer": "scathing"
    },
    {
      "question": "scenario",
      "answer": "scenario"
    },
    {
      "question": "schedule",
      "answer": "schedule"
    },
    {
      "question": "scissors",
      "answer": "scissors"
    },
    {
      "question": "scornful",
      "answer": "scornful"
    },
    {
      "question": "scrabble",
      "answer": "scrabble"
    },
    {
      "question": "scramble",
      "answer": "scramble"
    },
    {
      "question": "scribble",
      "answer": "scribble"
    },
    {
      "question": "scrutiny",
      "answer": "scrutiny"
    },
    {
      "question": "seamless",
      "answer": "seamless"
    },
    {
      "question": "seashore",
      "answer": "seashore"
    },
    {
      "question": "seasonal",
      "answer": "seasonal"
    },
    {
      "question": "secluded",
      "answer": "secluded"
    },
    {
      "question": "secondly",
      "answer": "secondly"
    },
    {
      "question": "secretly",
      "answer": "secretly"
    },
    {
      "question": "security",
      "answer": "security"
    },
    {
      "question": "sedative",
      "answer": "sedative"
    },
    {
      "question": "sediment",
      "answer": "sediment"
    },
    {
      "question": "selector",
      "answer": "selector"
    },
    {
      "question": "semantic",
      "answer": "semantic"
    },
    {
      "question": "semester",
      "answer": "semester"
    },
    {
      "question": "seminary",
      "answer": "seminary"
    },
    {
      "question": "sensible",
      "answer": "sensible"
    },
    {
      "question": "sentence",
      "answer": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "question": "separate",
      "answer": "separate"
    },
    {
      "question": "sequence",
      "answer": "sequence"
    },
    {
      "question": "sergeant",
      "answer": "sergeant"
    },
    {
      "question": "severely",
      "answer": "severely"
    },
    {
      "question": "severity",
      "answer": "severity"
    },
    {
      "question": "sewerage",
      "answer": "sewerage"
    },
    {
      "question": "shameful",
      "answer": "shameful"
    },
    {
      "question": "sheepish",
      "answer": "sheepish"
    },
    {
      "question": "shepherd",
      "answer": "shepherd"
    },
    {
      "question": "shilling",
      "answer": "shilling"
    },
    {
      "question": "shipping",
      "answer": "shipping"
    },
    {
      "question": "shocking",
      "answer": "shocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "shoelace",
      "answer": "shoelace"
    },
    {
      "question": "shoplift",
      "answer": "shoplift"
    },
    {
      "question": "shopping",
      "answer": "shopping"
    },
    {
      "question": "shortage",
      "answer": "shortage"
    },
    {
      "question": "shoulder",
      "answer": "shoulder"
    },
    {
      "question": "showcase",
      "answer": "showcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "showdown",
      "answer": "showdown"
    },
    {
      "question": "showroom",
      "answer": "showroom"
    },
    {
      "question": "sickness",
      "answer": "sickness"
    },
    {
      "question": "sideline",
      "answer": "sideline"
    },
    {
      "question": "sidewalk",
      "answer": "sidewalk"
    },
    {
      "question": "sideways",
      "answer": "sideways"
    },
    {
      "question": "signpost",
      "answer": "signpost"
    },
    {
      "question": "silently",
      "answer": "silently"
    },
    {
      "question": "simplify",
      "answer": "simplify"
    },
    {
      "question": "simulate",
      "answer": "simulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "sinecure",
      "answer": "sinecure"
    },
    {
      "question": "singular",
      "answer": "singular"
    },
    {
      "question": "sinister",
      "answer": "sinister"
    },
    {
      "question": "situated",
      "answer": "situated"
    },
    {
      "question": "sixtieth",
      "answer": "sixtieth"
    },
    {
      "question": "skillful",
      "answer": "skillful"
    },
    {
      "question": "skirmish",
      "answer": "skirmish"
    },
    {
      "question": "slightly",
      "answer": "slightly"
    },
    {
      "question": "slippery",
      "answer": "slippery"
    },
    {
      "question": "slovenly",
      "answer": "slovenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "sluggish",
      "answer": "sluggish"
    },
    {
      "question": "snowball",
      "answer": "snowball"
    },
    {
      "question": "software",
      "answer": "software"
    },
    {
      "question": "solemnly",
      "answer": "solemnly"
    },
    {
      "question": "solitary",
      "answer": "solitary"
    },
    {
      "question": "solitude",
      "answer": "solitude"
    },
    {
      "question": "solstice",
      "answer": "solstice"
    },
    {
      "question": "solution",
      "answer": "solution"
    },
    {
      "question": "somebody",
      "answer": "somebody"
    },
    {
      "question": "sometime",
      "answer": "sometime"
    },
    {
      "question": "somewhat",
      "answer": "somewhat"
    },
    {
      "question": "sorcerer",
      "answer": "sorcerer"
    },
    {
      "question": "southern",
      "answer": "southern"
    },
    {
      "question": "souvenir",
      "answer": "souvenir"
    },
    {
      "question": "speaking",
      "answer": "speaking"
    },
    {
      "question": "specific",
      "answer": "specific"
    },
    {
      "question": "specimen",
      "answer": "specimen"
    },
    {
      "question": "specious",
      "answer": "specious"
    },
    {
      "question": "spectrum",
      "answer": "spectrum"
    },
    {
      "question": "spelling",
      "answer": "spelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "spinning",
      "answer": "spinning"
    },
    {
      "question": "splendid",
      "answer": "splendid"
    },
    {
      "question": "splendor",
      "answer": "splendor"
    },
    {
      "question": "splinter",
      "answer": "splinter"
    },
    {
      "question": "spoonful",
      "answer": "spoonful"
    },
    {
      "question": "sporadic",
      "answer": "sporadic"
    },
    {
      "question": "sporting",
      "answer": "sporting"
    },
    {
      "question": "sprinkle",
      "answer": "sprinkle"
    },
    {
      "question": "spurious",
      "answer": "spurious"
    },
    {
      "question": "squabble",
      "answer": "squabble"
    },
    {
      "question": "squadron",
      "answer": "squadron"
    },
    {
      "question": "squander",
      "answer": "squander"
    },
    {
      "question": "squarely",
      "answer": "squarely"
    },
    {
      "question": "squatter",
      "answer": "squatter"
    },
    {
      "question": "squirrel",
      "answer": "squirrel"
    },
    {
      "question": "stagnant",
      "answer": "stagnant"
    },
    {
      "question": "stagnate",
      "answer": "stagnate"
    },
    {
      "question": "stairway",
      "answer": "stairway"
    },
    {
      "question": "stallion",
      "answer": "stallion"
    },
    {
      "question": "stalwart",
      "answer": "stalwart"
    },
    {
      "question": "standard",
      "answer": "standard"
    },
    {
      "question": "standing",
      "answer": "standing"
    },
    {
      "question": "steadily",
      "answer": "steadily"
    },
    {
      "question": "stealthy",
      "answer": "stealthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "sterling",
      "answer": "sterling"
    },
    {
      "question": "stimulus",
      "answer": "stimulus"
    },
    {
      "question": "stirring",
      "answer": "stirring"
    },
    {
      "question": "stocking",
      "answer": "stocking"
    },
    {
      "question": "stopover",
      "answer": "stopover"
    },
    {
      "question": "stoppage",
      "answer": "stoppage"
    },
    {
      "question": "straight",
      "answer": "straight"
    },
    {
      "question": "stranger",
      "answer": "stranger"
    },
    {
      "question": "strategy",
      "answer": "strategy"
    },
    {
      "question": "strength",
      "answer": "strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "stricken",
      "answer": "stricken"
    },
    {
      "question": "strictly",
      "answer": "strictly"
    },
    {
      "question": "strident",
      "answer": "strident"
    },
    {
      "question": "striking",
      "answer": "striking"
    },
    {
      "question": "strongly",
      "answer": "strongly"
    },
    {
      "question": "struggle",
      "answer": "struggle"
    },
    {
      "question": "stubborn",
      "answer": "stubborn"
    },
    {
      "question": "stunning",
      "answer": "stunning"
    },
    {
      "question": "subgroup",
      "answer": "subgroup"
    },
    {
      "question": "subtlety",
      "answer": "subtlety"
    },
    {
      "question": "subtract",
      "answer": "subtract"
    },
    {
      "question": "succinct",
      "answer": "succinct"
    },
    {
      "question": "suddenly",
      "answer": "suddenly"
    },
    {
      "question": "sufferer",
      "answer": "sufferer"
    },
    {
      "question": "suffrage",
      "answer": "suffrage"
    },
    {
      "question": "suicidal",
      "answer": "suicidal"
    },
    {
      "question": "suitable",
      "answer": "suitable"
    },
    {
      "question": "suitcase",
      "answer": "suitcase"
    },
    {
      "question": "sunlight",
      "answer": "sunlight"
    },
    {
      "question": "sunshine",
      "answer": "sunshine"
    },
    {
      "question": "superior",
      "answer": "superior"
    },
    {
      "question": "supplant",
      "answer": "supplant"
    },
    {
      "question": "supplier",
      "answer": "supplier"
    },
    {
      "question": "supposed",
      "answer": "supposed"
    },
    {
      "question": "suppress",
      "answer": "suppress"
    },
    {
      "question": "surgical",
      "answer": "surgical"
    },
    {
      "question": "surmount",
      "answer": "surmount"
    },
    {
      "question": "surprise",
      "answer": "surprise"
    },
    {
      "question": "surround",
      "answer": "surround"
    },
    {
      "question": "surveyor",
      "answer": "surveyor"
    },
    {
      "question": "survival",
      "answer": "survival"
    },
    {
      "question": "survivor",
      "answer": "survivor"
    },
    {
      "question": "suspense",
      "answer": "suspense"
    },
    {
      "question": "sweeping",
      "answer": "sweeping"
    },
    {
      "question": "swelling",
      "answer": "swelling"
    },
    {
      "question": "swimsuit",
      "answer": "swimsuit"
    },
    {
      "question": "syllable",
      "answer": "syllable"
    },
    {
      "question": "syllabus",
      "answer": "syllabus"
    },
    {
      "question": "symbolic",
      "answer": "symbolic"
    },
    {
      "question": "symmetry",
      "answer": "symmetry"
    },
    {
      "question": "sympathy",
      "answer": "sympathy"
    },
    {
      "question": "symphony",
      "answer": "symphony"
    },
    {
      "question": "syndrome",
      "answer": "syndrome"
    },
    {
      "question": "synopsis",
      "answer": "synopsis"
    },
    {
      "question": "tactical",
      "answer": "tactical"
    },
    {
      "question": "talented",
      "answer": "talented"
    },
    {
      "question": "talisman",
      "answer": "talisman"
    },
    {
      "question": "tangible",
      "answer": "tangible"
    },
    {
      "question": "tasteful",
      "answer": "tasteful"
    },
    {
      "question": "taxation",
      "answer": "taxation"
    },
    {
      "question": "taxpayer",
      "answer": "taxpayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "teaching",
      "answer": "teaching"
    },
    {
      "question": "teammate",
      "answer": "teammate"
    },
    {
      "question": "teamwork",
      "answer": "teamwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "teaspoon",
      "answer": "teaspoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "telegram",
      "answer": "telegram"
    },
    {
      "question": "televise",
      "answer": "televise"
    },
    {
      "question": "temporal",
      "answer": "temporal"
    },
    {
      "question": "tendency",
      "answer": "tendency"
    },
    {
      "question": "tenderly",
      "answer": "tenderly"
    },
    {
      "question": "tenement",
      "answer": "tenement"
    },
    {
      "question": "tentacle",
      "answer": "tentacle"
    },
    {
      "question": "terminal",
      "answer": "terminal"
    },
    {
      "question": "terminus",
      "answer": "terminus"
    },
    {
      "question": "terrible",
      "answer": "terrible"
    },
    {
      "question": "terribly",
      "answer": "terribly"
    },
    {
      "question": "terrific",
      "answer": "terrific"
    },
    {
      "question": "textbook",
      "answer": "textbook"
    },
    {
      "question": "thankful",
      "answer": "thankful"
    },
    {
      "question": "theology",
      "answer": "theology"
    },
    {
      "question": "thinking",
      "answer": "thinking"
    },
    {
      "question": "thirteen",
      "answer": "thirteen"
    },
    {
      "question": "thorough",
      "answer": "thorough"
    },
    {
      "question": "thousand",
      "answer": "thousand"
    },
    {
      "question": "threaten",
      "answer": "threaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "thriller",
      "answer": "thriller"
    },
    {
      "question": "throttle",
      "answer": "throttle"
    },
    {
      "question": "thursday",
      "answer": "thursday"
    },
    {
      "question": "timeless",
      "answer": "timeless"
    },
    {
      "question": "timidity",
      "answer": "timidity"
    },
    {
      "question": "tireless",
      "answer": "tireless"
    },
    {
      "question": "tiresome",
      "answer": "tiresome"
    },
    {
      "question": "together",
      "answer": "together"
    },
    {
      "question": "tolerant",
      "answer": "tolerant"
    },
    {
      "question": "tolerate",
      "answer": "tolerate"
    },
    {
      "question": "tomorrow",
      "answer": "tomorrow"
    },
    {
      "question": "tortoise",
      "answer": "tortoise"
    },
    {
      "question": "touching",
      "answer": "touching"
    },
    {
      "question": "towering",
      "answer": "towering"
    },
    {
      "question": "township",
      "answer": "township"
    },
    {
      "question": "training",
      "answer": "training"
    },
    {
      "question": "tranquil",
      "answer": "tranquil"
    },
    {
      "question": "transact",
      "answer": "transact"
    },
    {
      "question": "transfer",
      "answer": "transfer"
    },
    {
      "question": "transmit",
      "answer": "transmit"
    },
    {
      "question": "traveler",
      "answer": "traveler"
    },
    {
      "question": "treasure",
      "answer": "treasure"
    },
    {
      "question": "treasury",
      "answer": "treasury"
    },
    {
      "question": "treatise",
      "answer": "treatise"
    },
    {
      "question": "trespass",
      "answer": "trespass"
    },
    {
      "question": "triangle",
      "answer": "triangle"
    },
    {
      "question": "tribunal",
      "answer": "tribunal"
    },
    {
      "question": "trillion",
      "answer": "trillion"
    },
    {
      "question": "trimming",
      "answer": "trimming"
    },
    {
      "question": "trombone",
      "answer": "trombone"
    },
    {
      "question": "tropical",
      "answer": "tropical"
    },
    {
      "question": "trousers",
      "answer": "trousers"
    },
    {
      "question": "trusting",
      "answer": "trusting"
    },
    {
      "question": "truthful",
      "answer": "truthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "turnover",
      "answer": "turnover"
    },
    {
      "question": "turnpike",
      "answer": "turnpike"
    },
    {
      "question": "tutorial",
      "answer": "tutorial"
    },
    {
      "question": "twilight",
      "answer": "twilight"
    },
    {
      "question": "ultimate",
      "answer": "ultimate"
    },
    {
      "question": "umbrella",
      "answer": "umbrella"
    },
    {
      "question": "unbeaten",
      "answer": "unbeaten"
    },
    {
      "question": "unbutton",
      "answer": "unbutton"
    },
    {
      "question": "uncommon",
      "answer": "uncommon"
    },
    {
      "question": "undercut",
      "answer": "undercut"
    },
    {
      "question": "underpin",
      "answer": "underpin"
    },
    {
      "question": "underway",
      "answer": "underway"
    },
    {
      "question": "ungainly",
      "answer": "ungainly"
    },
    {
      "question": "unionist",
      "answer": "unionist"
    },
    {
      "question": "universe",
      "answer": "universe"
    },
    {
      "question": "unlikely",
      "answer": "unlikely"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsettle",
      "answer": "unsettle"
    },
    {
      "question": "unspoken",
      "answer": "unspoken"
    },
    {
      "question": "unsteady",
      "answer": "unsteady"
    },
    {
      "question": "untimely",
      "answer": "untimely"
    },
    {
      "question": "unworthy",
      "answer": "unworthy"
    },
    {
      "question": "upheaval",
      "answer": "upheaval"
    },
    {
      "question": "upmarket",
      "answer": "upmarket"
    },
    {
      "question": "uprising",
      "answer": "uprising"
    },
    {
      "question": "upstairs",
      "answer": "upstairs"
    },
    {
      "question": "vacation",
      "answer": "vacation"
    },
    {
      "question": "vagabond",
      "answer": "vagabond"
    },
    {
      "question": "validate",
      "answer": "validate"
    },
    {
      "question": "validity",
      "answer": "validity"
    },
    {
      "question": "valuable",
      "answer": "valuable"
    },
    {
      "question": "vanguard",
      "answer": "vanguard"
    },
    {
      "question": "vanquish",
      "answer": "vanquish"
    },
    {
      "question": "variable",
      "answer": "variable"
    },
    {
      "question": "vehement",
      "answer": "vehement"
    },
    {
      "question": "venomous",
      "answer": "venomous"
    },
    {
      "question": "vertical",
      "answer": "vertical"
    },
    {
      "question": "vicinity",
      "answer": "vicinity"
    },
    {
      "question": "vigilant",
      "answer": "vigilant"
    },
    {
      "question": "vigorous",
      "answer": "vigorous"
    },
    {
      "question": "villager",
      "answer": "villager"
    },
    {
      "question": "violence",
      "answer": "violence"
    },
    {
      "question": "virtuous",
      "answer": "virtuous"
    },
    {
      "question": "vitality",
      "answer": "vitality"
    },
    {
      "question": "vocation",
      "answer": "vocation"
    },
    {
      "question": "volatile",
      "answer": "volatile"
    },
    {
      "question": "volition",
      "answer": "volition"
    },
    {
      "question": "waitress",
      "answer": "waitress"
    },
    {
      "question": "wanderer",
      "answer": "wanderer"
    },
    {
      "question": "warranty",
      "answer": "warranty"
    },
    {
      "question": "wasteful",
      "answer": "wasteful"
    },
    {
      "question": "watchdog",
      "answer": "watchdog"
    },
    {
      "question": "watchful",
      "answer": "watchful"
    },
    {
      "question": "watchman",
      "answer": "watchman"
    },
    {
      "question": "watering",
      "answer": "watering"
    },
    {
      "question": "weakness",
      "answer": "weakness"
    },
    {
      "question": "westward",
      "answer": "westward"
    },
    {
      "question": "whatever",
      "answer": "whatever"
    },
    {
      "question": "whenever",
      "answer": "whenever"
    },
    {
      "question": "wherever",
      "answer": "wherever"
    },
    {
      "question": "wildlife",
      "answer": "wildlife"
    },
    {
      "question": "windfall",
      "answer": "windfall"
    },
    {
      "question": "wireless",
      "answer": "wireless"
    },
    {
      "question": "withdraw",
      "answer": "withdraw"
    },
    {
      "question": "woodland",
      "answer": "woodland"
    },
    {
      "question": "woodwork",
      "answer": "woodwork"
    },
    {
      "question": "workable",
      "answer": "workable"
    },
    {
      "question": "workshop",
      "answer": "workshop"
    },
    {
      "question": "worrying",
      "answer": "worrying"
    },
    {
      "question": "wreckage",
      "answer": "wreckage"
    },
    {
      "question": "wrestler",
      "answer": "wrestler"
    },
    {
      "question": "wretched",
      "answer": "wretched"
    },
    {
      "question": "yearning",
      "answer": "yearning"
    },
    {
      "question": "yielding",
      "answer": "yielding"
    },
    {
      "question": "yourself",
      "answer": "yourself"
    },
    {
      "question": "youthful",
      "answer": "youthful"
    },
    {
      "question": "greatest",
      "answer": "greatest"
    },
    {
      "question": "creative",
      "answer": "creative"
    },
    {
      "question": "spending",
      "answer": "spending"
    },
    {
      "question": "designer",
      "answer": "designer"
    },
    {
      "question": "teenager",
      "answer": "teenager"
    },
    {
      "question": "criteria",
      "answer": "criteria"
    },
    {
      "question": "advocate",
      "answer": "advocate"
    },
    {
      "question": "shooting",
      "answer": "shooting"
    },
    {
      "question": "earnings",
      "answer": "earnings"
    },
    {
      "question": "proposed",
      "answer": "proposed"
    },
    {
      "question": "fighting",
      "answer": "fighting"
    },
    {
      "question": "changing",
      "answer": "changing"
    },
    {
      "question": "suburban",
      "answer": "suburban"
    },
    {
      "question": "starting",
      "answer": "starting"
    },
    {
      "question": "judicial",
      "answer": "judicial"
    },
    {
      "question": "minimize",
      "answer": "minimize"
    },
    {
      "question": "annually",
      "answer": "annually"
    },
    {
      "question": "sexually",
      "answer": "sexually"
    },
    {
      "question": "dynamics",
      "answer": "dynamics"
    },
    {
      "question": "parental",
      "answer": "parental"
    },
    {
      "question": "improved",
      "answer": "improved"
    },
    {
      "question": "homeland",
      "answer": "homeland"
    },
    {
      "question": "casualty",
      "answer": "casualty"
    },
    {
      "question": "expected",
      "answer": "expected"
    },
    {
      "question": "interact",
      "answer": "interact"
    },
    {
      "question": "disabled",
      "answer": "disabled"
    },
    {
      "question": "swimming",
      "answer": "swimming"
    },
    {
      "question": "required",
      "answer": "required"
    },
    {
      "question": "emerging",
      "answer": "emerging"
    },
    {
      "question": "retailer",
      "answer": "retailer"
    },
    {
      "question": "artifact",
      "answer": "artifact"
    },
    {
      "question": "socially",
      "answer": "socially"
    },
    {
      "question": "isolated",
      "answer": "isolated"
    },
    {
      "question": "lawmaker",
      "answer": "lawmaker"
    },
    {
      "question": "autonomy",
      "answer": "autonomy"
    },
    {
      "question": "landmark",
      "answer": "landmark"
    },
    {
      "question": "explicit",
      "answer": "explicit"
    },
    {
      "question": "troubled",
      "answer": "troubled"
    },
    {
      "question": "balanced",
      "answer": "balanced"
    },
    {
      "question": "managing",
      "answer": "managing"
    },
    {
      "question": "epidemic",
      "answer": "epidemic"
    },
    {
      "question": "selected",
      "answer": "selected"
    }
  ]
}